const englishPartOfSpeechQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is the part of speech for the word 'happy' in the sentence 'She is very happy'?",
      options: ["Noun", "Adjective", "Verb", "Adverb"],
      correct_option: "Adjective"
    },
    {
      question: "Which part of speech is used to show an action or state of being?",
      options: ["Adjective", "Noun", "Verb", "Pronoun"],
      correct_option: "Verb"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the part of speech for the word 'quickly' in the sentence 'He ran quickly'?",
      options: ["Adjective", "Noun", "Verb", "Adverb"],
      correct_option: "Adverb"
    },
    {
      question: "Which part of speech is used to replace a noun?",
      options: ["Adverb", "Preposition", "Pronoun", "Conjunction"],
      correct_option: "Pronoun"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the part of speech for the word 'apple' in the sentence 'She ate an apple'?",
      options: ["Noun", "Adjective", "Verb", "Adverb"],
      correct_option: "Noun"
    },
    {
      question: "Which part of speech connects words or groups of words?",
      options: ["Interjection", "Pronoun", "Conjunction", "Adverb"],
      correct_option: "Conjunction"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the part of speech for the word 'happily' in the sentence 'She smiled happily'?",
      options: ["Adjective", "Noun", "Verb", "Adverb"],
      correct_option: "Adverb"
    },
    {
      question: "Which part of speech is used to express strong emotion and is often followed by an exclamation mark?",
      options: ["Adverb", "Pronoun", "Interjection", "Conjunction"],
      correct_option: "Interjection"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the part of speech for the word 'jumped' in the sentence 'The cat jumped onto the table'?",
      options: ["Noun", "Adjective", "Verb", "Adverb"],
      correct_option: "Verb"
    },
    {
      question: "Which part of speech is used to show the relationship between a noun or pronoun and other words in a sentence?",
      options: ["Adverb", "Preposition", "Conjunction", "Interjection"],
      correct_option: "Preposition"
    }
  ];
  
  export default englishPartOfSpeechQuestions
  // You can access each question and its properties using array indexing.
  